#### Contact

339-364-4334 (Mobile) yevgeniyabw@hotmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/yevgeniyawright-bsn-rn-ccrn-4b361157 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Customer Service
Training
Research

## Languages

Russian (Native or Bilingual) English (Full Professional)

#### Certifications

Basic Life Support for Healthcare Providers (BLS)

Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS)

Acute/Critical Care Nurse - Adult, Pediatric, Neonatal (CCRN)

Advanced Cardiovascular Life Support Experienced Provider (ACLS)

#### Honors-Awards

Three Time Daisy Award Nominee
Best in Care Award Nominee

# Yevgeniya Wright, BSN, RN, CCRN

Clinical Consultant at Baxter International Inc.

Greater Boston Area

## Summary

Experienced Intensive Care Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS), Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), Critical Care Nursing, Healthcare, and Cardiopulmonary Resuscitation (CPR). Strong healthcare services professional graduated from Regis College.

## Experience

Baxter International Inc.
Clinical Consultant
October 2019 - Present (9 months)

Boston Children's Hospital Critical Care Registered Nurse July 2015 - Present (5 years) Boston, Massachusetts

Cardiac Intensive Care Unit

St. Elizabeth's Medical Center Registered Nurse October 2014 - July 2015 (10 months)

Massasoit Community College Professional Tutor December 2010 - June 2015 (4 years 7 months)

# Education

Regis College

BSN, Public Health & Leadership and Management Minor, Registered Nursing/ Registered Nurse · (2011 - 2014)

Massasoit Community College
Associate of Science - AS, Liberal Arts and Sciences/Liberal
Studies · (2010 - 2011)